Come on, do the zeros shooting star waterfall top Happy New Year, everyone!
Hey, finally... we've started the New Year...
Isn't it too early to record? The one for New Year's.
It's October 17th!
It's still a little hot and you're wearing short sleeves!
But we're already in the New Year's mode on air.
Thank you all for your cooperation this year!
So, what are we going to do today?
This time, I'd like you to thank someone.
Thanks?
Who is it?
This person.
Is that him? Chris Matsumura before he sold out, right?
No, that's not him.
Is that my partner?
This is Mr. Chuei.
I'd like you to thank Mr. Chuei.
Me?
I saw your national tour the other day.
The two of you were so cool as comic dancers.
I'm so happy!
I hope you two will continue to work well together.
I hope you guys will continue to work well together.
I'm a little embarrassed about it.
It's fine to just say thank you, of course.
But since we are here in Hida Takayama, a place with a lot of nature
I would like to make a present and give it to you.
Not just words.
Yes.
A present would be nice too.
Absolutely not!
I'm supposed to make it, right?
No, not for the time being.
You're right.
But you don't want to do it alone, do you?
That's why I've invited some encouraging guests.
Guest.
Congratulations!
Congratulations! Oh, what's that?
We've got two more of these two different color groups here...
The morning chime has rung!
I'm Kaho Kobayashi, attendance number 11 from Ebituate School!
Please give me a warm welcome!
I've been the MC of Ebiture's show for a long time.
Since the time when Kaho Kobayashi joined the group.
That's right, for about 10 years now.
The reason why we are inviting Mr. Kobayashi this time is
He has a talent for art.
I've done some classics before.
I am a self-proclaimed cultured person in Ebitu.
Self-proclaimed?
I'm a self-proclaimed cultured person.
I'm a self-proclaimed cultured person, and I've been treated well.
I'm a direct junior of Mr. Shooting Star.
I've done the preaching for our solo shows.
He's on a nationwide tour.
That's why I came here.
Do you know why I came?
Because of Art of Commencias.
I'm kind of in the same boat.
I can put all my clothes on in 10 seconds.
I can tuck everything I'm wearing into my pants within 10 seconds.
How close are we?
Not even close.
I thought maybe you could give me some advice.
Where's the later part?
Why don't you ask Mr. Kobayashi to hide it for you?
Count to 10 seconds.
Yes, sir.
Ten seconds.
Okay, then.
Is it enough?
Are you okay? What are you doing to my idol?
Here we go.
One. One.
Two.
Three.
Start 456789, one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
All right, put it down, put it down, put it down.
Yes, sir.
Where's the art in that?
It's meant to contain your anger towards Shuei.
I mean to put away my anger towards you.
I'm so angry at you right now.
Shooting Stars will celebrate their 25th anniversary this year.
But until now, we've often worried our fans with rumors of discord and flame wars.
But they've often worried their fans with rumors of discord and flame wars.
A university student producer who worries about you two more than anyone else...
With a strong desire to support the two of them
Takigami-san devised a project to express his gratitude to his partner, Nakae-san.
This time, Mr. Takigami, who is so talented in art that he has held a private exhibition
Shiritsu Ebisu Chugaku Mr. Kobayashi, who is so talented in art that he has opened his own private exhibition, and
and Mr. Kobayashi, a young duo with deep faith, who has performed as the front section of a live performance of “Shooting Stars
Mr. Ryosei of Mr. Dai-boken, a young duo
Mr. Ryosei of Mr. Great Adventure
in Takayama, a place famous for its lumber.
to deepen their relationship
to deepen their relationship.
Mr. Kakigami will surprise Mr. Nakanaga with the gift.
Mr. Kakigami is going to tell Ms. Nakanaga what he's been thinking about for the past 25 years.
I'll be honest. I'm almost in tears.
A change of clothes... That's nice.
It's better this way.
Hello hello hello yes, this is better this way this way is better
Oh, hi.
Please. Hello.
Hello.
My name is Komaya. I'm from Komaya Corporation.
Mr. Komaya. Nice to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
No, no, no, no.
Thank you for watching this teacup from the side.
This time, I'm going to help you with a little tail recording.
I hope we can make a wonderful present for you.
Please take a look at the showroom.
I'd be happy to escort you to the showroom and talk about what we're going to make today.
I would be happy to escort you to the showroom and talk about what we are going to make today.
I see.
The company we will be working with this time is a furniture maker, Mr. Komaeya, who has been in business for over 30 years.
Kozenya, a furniture maker loved in Hita Takayama
They manufacture and sell custom-made furniture and accessories.
Their handmade furniture made by craftsmen is very popular.
Wow!
What, what, what, what?
Mr. Camera, no one is following us!
There you are, there you are, there you are, there you are!
This is amazing!
The wood smells so good, it smells so good!
It's made by Hida's master craftsmen.
It's quite expensive, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
The most expensive one here...
This one is especially made of a single piece of wood
Only the best part of one tree is used.
About 2 million.
Two million.
This is a single piece of wood, right?
Since we're here, we're going to borrow a table that's worth 2.75 million yen.
Let's regress to see what we can make together.
This place is so comfortable to the touch.
It's so comfortable to the touch.
But you're right.
Smooth, isn't it?
Smooth
Do you have a desk?
They're pretty expensive.
I have an expensive one.
It's called Nitori.
I know, I know.
You're drooling.
You're drooling because I gave you so many instructions.
But that's beside the point.
A present for Mr. Chuei!
Let's decide!
I don't think a table is too much to ask for.
Let's see what I can come up with.
Takayama is also a production center of chairs.
It's especially famous for making chairs.
This time, I'm going to have them make chairs.
You've already decided?
The chair is the best way to express our gratitude.
No, no, no, I like the clock... The chair is the most appreciative.
No, no, no, I thought that clock was really nice.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't like the chair?
No, I mean...
It's not good?
We've made a lot of arrangements.
Hey, there!
What's going on!
I don't have a choice.
But I don't like it.
Don't make a face like you don't know what you're talking about.
But it's not right.
I'm just trying to make you feel appreciated.
I'm trying to be appreciative, and you say something like this.
To be honest, your attitude is weird to begin with.
No, no, no, no. I thought it was all very arranged.
This time, the chair to be made is this one.
It's already decided.
It's like a cooking show.
It's a little...
It'll never break.
You know...
I had this feeling that I wanted us to be together.
Emotions.
Furniture with folds.
It's Job.
That's right, isn't it?
I see.
Shape it as you would, Mr. Takigami.
I'll have them do the work for me.
I see. You can do that.
I'll try to imagine Mr. Chuei as much as possible.
He's got a bad back and a bad elbow God, and his posture is getting better and better
I want him to be able to squat... but I guess we'll just have to make him a nice chair.
Let's make a nice chair for Mr. A.
Let's start with the design.
Based on the draft we received from the coma shop
We all came up with ideas based on the draft we received from the koma shop.
Can we use the help of Mr. Kobayashi here?
Yes, that would be great.
I'm good at art.
What do you think of Nakai-san, Mr. Takei?
I think it's too shaggy.
It has to be external.
That's good.
A rounded head in form.
You can do that on the seat of the chair.
Can you make it shaggy here too? You can do that, you can do that, you can do that, you can do that.
I'm sure it's a lot of work, but this one looks like a medium.
For example, I'd like to have a shooting star here.
Engraving.
Isn't that a good idea?
With Kobayashi's sense of style, we could do something like that here.
A shooting star in the middle of a shooting star, and if you imagine a shooting star...
I'd like to see what you'd draw on it.
I'll get right on it.
That was quick.
It's been there for a long time.
Yes, sir.
Shooting star
I've already done it during the on-air battle. Shooting star
It's the one we did during the on-air battle.
Because I'm a fan.
It's from a fan's point of view.
It's a little bit core.
It's not like we're going back to the basics.
It's not like we're going back to the basics, but we're trying to move forward.
But, you know...
Kobayashi said a nostalgic word
A shooting star, a nostalgic word.
I was feeling a little emo back then.
But I won't know until I make it.
It's terrible.
Takigami-san, you're not so honest, are you?
Now that the design has been decided, it's time to start building the stone!
I'd like to call in a few people to guide us.
Please, please, please, please, please, please...
How's it coming along?
Yes, we'll make it, but it's a little difficult to find the right part.
I think the head part might be a little difficult, but I don't think she'll be able to do it.
That part might be difficult, that part might be difficult
That's the hard part
That's the hard part.
Worst-case scenario, you could do it later.
No...
Please don't do that.
Making a chair for Mr. Nakae
The next step is cutting.
Let's work together.
I'll totally cooperate.
I'm counting on you.
I'll do my best.
I'd like one of you to draw a line on behalf of the others.
First of all...
Mr. Takeuchi, for the first time.
That's right.
I hope you're doing well
I don't know how to write this.
I don't know...
Should I do it from the back?
If you could write it as you think once
Chuei's head was like this.
Yes, yes, yes, remembering that.
Thinking about it.
Yes, yes, yes.
I was thinking back to the time when I was sticking my head in...
I'm sorry, is it like this?
Wait a minute... wait a minute...
It's too messy!
Is this okay?
A little bigger.
Like this...
The bigger the wave, the bigger the wave, the bigger the wave, the bigger the wave.
The bigger the wave, the bigger the wave.
The fewer times you have to shave it.
What were you like in high school?
He was a dapper guy, anyway.
He lived in a dorm. I went to his dorm room.
I don't know if he thought it was cool to speak English in high school.
I don't know if he thought it was cool to be in high school or what, but he had empty Pringles cans all lined up on the wall.
But it's kind of understandable.
They're imported. They're all in English.
So you weren't a cool guy? In high school.
I decided to get a perm.
I see.
And my mom is a hairdresser.
So I gave her a cool perm.
It went crazy here.
Like Bach!
Bach and Chuei work well together!
How is it better than before?
Yes, it's much better than before.
Now that we've finished the draft, it's time to move on to the cut!
Mr. Takigami, please put your heart and soul into it and do your best.
Then let's do it.
You're already early.
Amazing.
This is it, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
I'll ask him to back up.
That's right.
I'm going to have to ask you to back up.
Only the back?
It's so hard.
Can an amateur do it?
Let's hand over to Ryosei.
I'm sure you'll fix it.
Okay, not too much shaving... and then pass the baton to Ryosei.
Okay, not too much shaving.
No, no, no, I'll do something else. It's too far inside.
Kobayashi, are you sure?
Kobayashi, who has artistic talent, will try again.
No hesitation.
What a surprise!
I'm here as a helper, right?
Is this okay?
This might not work.
I'm sorry.
But that's my foot, too.
This is also a foot.
Nice follow-up, Mr. Takigami!
At any rate, I'm glad you didn't get hurt!
While Mr. Takigami, who is getting used to cutting, was finishing up
Ryosei-san asked me this question
Have you been telling him for a long time? Is there anything you want to thank me for? While Ryosei-san was finishing up, Ryosei-san asked me this question
Have you been telling him for a long time? Thank you.
Do you have a thank you?
No, I don't.
No thank you?
Maybe no thank you.
Maybe you too, Chuei.
If you get this when it's finished
I'm sure he'll be very embarrassed.
He'll probably say something backhanded.
And you won't lose?
Shut up, you guys.
Why?
I'm serious.
Why should I get mad?
I'm asking you a lot of questions.
What do you think? I'm fine.
I'm fine.
You're half-smiling.
I'm sure it's fine.
May I ask you to make some changes?
Sure.
A little.
We're amateurs.
May I ask you to check it under the guidance of a craftsman? We are amateurs.
Under the guidance of the craftsman, we cut the seat surface and proceed to the next step.
Making a chair for Mr. Nakae. Next, we polish the cut parts.
Then we will polish them with this machine.
- Amazing! If you could turn it like this, aiming at the line you just saw...
I see.
Then, may I have a word?
Please bring it to me.
She said she wanted to do it herself.
As you can see...
This is fun.
I was scared before.
But this one, I don't have to worry about my life.
If you touch this, you'll bleed.
It's dangerous.
Please don't pretend to be a comedian. It's dangerous.
I'll be like, “Please do it.
That's the scariest thing of all.
With the help of Mr. Kobayashi and Ryosei
Mr. Kobayashi and Mr. Ryosei are helping us out, and we're making good progress.
Finally, Mr. Takigami will make the final touches.
He's starting to get a little attached to it.
He's getting pretty attached to it.
He's been polishing it for a long time, even though I told him to hurry up and finish it when he complained about it.
Mr. Takigami's expression is more serious than ever.
It seems his feelings for Tadahide-san are getting a little stronger.
Now...
Beautiful!
Good, good, good.
The balance is also nice
Making a chair for Mr. Tadahide
Next, assembling the parts
We have a veteran craftsman with 40 years of experience in this field.
A veteran craftsman with 40 years of experience in this field will help us.
First of all, he put glue here.
Then we're going to use a hammer to put this here.
We'll put this in here, and then we'll do the final check here.
Put the glue on and try to put it together.
Yu Taguchi, do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
He's already talking to me like I'm his friend.
That's not what I meant.
He's talking to you as if you're his friend.
We've known each other a long time.
Oh, that's right.
If we'd known each other longer, I'd probably have hit him.
Watch out!
I'd have to go all out to get in.
I'll hold you up.
You'll support me?
I see.
Go for it.
I'm gonna go hold him down.
Is that right?
Come on.
I think we're good.
You got a second?
Both lines?
We're like judges, we're supposed to be talking over each other, or we're supposed to be talking over each other, or I'm supposed to be talking over each other.
I thought you'd say, “No, I'm not supporting you,” but then you started making different moves.
You're starting to make a different move, too.
I thought you were supporting me.
I didn't think you were a blur.
Please cooperate with each other.
Kobayashi, you're up next.
Let me sleep.
Lay him down.
Face down.
Like this.
Like this
And then hit it with a hammer on that side.
like this
Lay it down on this side
And then...
Like this?
Oh, this side.
I see.
And now...
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
Sorry. Wrong side.
Wait a minute.
You're waiting.
There's more...
I only need about half of it.
Assembly is progressing smoothly.
Okay, Kobayashi-san, it's okay.
I'm scared.
Kobayashi, is it okay? I'm scared, I'm scared.
It's okay.
That's enough.
Legs are done.
That's almost it... one more letter.
Not even close.
Mr. Takigami, it's not finished yet!
Next, we'll fit the legs into the seat.
They're not in yet?
Not yet.
Dad, it's hard to get in here.
I'm sorry.
It would have been fun if it broke.
With the help of the craftsman, the legs and seat are now joined.
Now we'll move on to the next step.
Make sure they don't come loose completely.
Here are four of them.
We're more than halfway through.
What?
It's true.
It's not like the Nitori ones.
It's not good.
Don't say that.
What's that?
Don't say it.
I'm not going to say too much, but Nitori has its own merits.
Don't say that! Don't say that!
It's too late.
Thank you, Nitori!
You see this sticking out?
Yes.
It's in the way.
That's right.
I want to punch it.
Wow!
Cut it off.
You do it with your hands.
By hand.
Not just the top wedge here, but the bottom.
Not only the top wedge here, but also the bottom round part.
If you stand it up, you can cut the bottom part.
This looks difficult.
Mr. Fairy managed to do it, too.
Next is Ms. Kobayashi.
I'm not so sure about this one.
Then, Ms. Kobayashi, please.
Are you sure? Is it okay?
It's already round. Just the top tip is fine.
That's right.
I'll put more in.
Oh, my God! That's hard! What is this?
As we were all struggling, the craftsman gave us a shocking revelation.
There's another way.
But you were good at it, weren't you?
You did it!
There's an even easier trick!
I wanted to be the first.
May I?
Including the one you worked so hard to cut.
That's all that's left, isn't it?
That's all that's left.
Are you sure you want to do that?
Are you kidding me? Is it okay?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's the last of it.
Why don't we just end it like this?
It's okay to do it the other way around.
That's right.
But...
But the sauce...
But it's gonna be so clean in no time.
Even for you.
Like it was all for nothing.
I know what's out there, but we've already done everything.
I'm just gonna put aside my desire to start from the beginning and move on to the next step.
Okay, now we're going to build the back support.
We're going to put up all the pillars in order.
Which one of you guys invited Mr. Shooting Star?
This is Nakae.
You're Mr. Nakae? This is Mr. Chuei.
Did you know he was Mr. Chuei?
We went to high school together and did comedy as a group of five.
But after high school, I went to Osaka for beauty school.
Chuey was a ronin in Tokyo.
One day, Chuey came to Osaka.
You're all I've got, you comedian.
I said, “Well, if you're going to bring me up so much, then I've got to go.
Later I heard there were five of us.
I was the last one, and you're the only one.
I'm embarrassed to admit it.
That could be what he said. So you were the only one for him?
It was a gradual rejection.
Did you accept him because he was Mr. Nakae?
But yes, his facial expressions were funny even in high school.
I always thought they were funny.
The fart smell... and farting in class.
He farted in class... and went to Chuei Hyogo again.
I'm glad to hear about the surprising secret of the battle of the shooting stars.
We'll get them all in in the end.
It's in, it's in, it's in.
It's okay.
Please say “stop”.
Of course, stop!
Where are you going to get more?
And...
Will it come out later?
Because the bomb will be crushed.
Let's not put it out afterwards.
This is no good.
This is a no-no.
It's in.
Yes, it's in.
It's a good combination.
After this, the assembly was proceeding smoothly.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Sorry for the wait.
As much as possible.
Excellent.
You've done a wonderful job.
It's as rounded as possible.
I like the flavor of it.
I'm honestly starting to enjoy it.
I'm having fun.
Well, then I'm grateful.
Yes, gratitude, that's right.
The joy of making things.
I'm not done yet.
Not yet.
I asked Mr. Takigami about the disagreement that once caused a stir.
I asked Mr. Takigami about the rumor that they didn't get along.
We had a fight at Godsun.
They had a fight at Godotan.
We had a hard time after that... but we made up soon after.
But when we went on the show... we didn't get along.
But when we went on the show, we had to act like we didn't get along with each other.
Narujo got turned on by it and said, “You're just like that...” and I got in on it.
Narujo got turned on by it, and he was like, “You're just like him, you know?
But I thought Kobayashi was great.
I went to see Ebichiyo's concert.
And when I went to greet him backstage...
Kobayashi told Ino no Ichiba
Well, let's be friends.
Oh, and use your strength.
Yeah.
I was so happy.
That's great!
I can say this, Mr. Kobayashi... wait a minute, wait a minute... yes, it made me so happy... that's great... that's you...
Wait a minute, wait a minute, I'm talking about something great.
You're like a director.
I'm like a director. Master, you're talking too much to my work.
It's our job, too.
There are seven holes, so let the seven threads go in a little bit.
Okay, okay, okay, other shigure, okay, let the staff's intention be to put a little bit in, okay, okay.
Okay, okay.
Okay, barking shishige, OK.
It's done.
Great.
It's starting to look a little more like a middle guard.
It's kind of nice.
It's really good.
It's good. It's better than I thought it would be.
Next week.
I've got a problem.
I'm going to finish the chair and tell Mr. Takigami what I've been keeping inside for 25 years.